卢伯克市
市政厅
建筑安全部
打扰一下
Excuse me.
-我能帮到你吗  -希望如此
- May I help you? ‭- Oh, I really hope so.
您需要什么帮助
What can I do for you?
我的律所递交了梅萨维德银行的图纸
Uh, my firm submitted plans for Mesa Verde Bank.
我们要在卢伯克建分行
We're building a branch here in Lubbock.
好的  我应该见过
Oh, sure, I think I saw that come through.
我在整理的时候
As I was cleaning up
内部归档所有图纸
re-filing all our plans internally
我发现少了一份之前的版本
I realized I was missing one of the old versions.
我们最后在会议室尺寸上有些修改
We had some late changes to the conference-room dimensions
所以出了好几份不同的版本
so there were different versions floating around
事情变得很复杂
and things got really complicated.
抱歉
Sorry.
长话短说  我觉得有可能
So, long story short, I think it's possible
错误的版本放进了我们的提案里
the wrong version ended up in our proposal.
-天啊  -是啊
- Oh, dear. ‭- Yeah.
我带了正确的版本来
So, I have the correct plans here
我想看一下
and I was hoping to just take a look
最后通过的版本  比对一下
at the approved plans to compare them
-以防万一  -好的  好的
- just to make sure. - ‭Okay. Okay.
但如果真搞错了
Um, but if they're wrong
你知道你得重新提交吧
you know you have to re-file --
重来  我知道
Re-file. Yeah. I know.
我就想确认一下是真的弄错了
I just want to make sure they actually are the wrong ones
免得给我老板添麻烦
before I, uh, ‭get into it with my bosses.
没问题
No problem.
-梅萨维德  -对
- Uh, Mesa Verde? - ‭Yes.
知道地址吗
Do you have the address?
贝勒街8783号
8783 Baylor Street.
我这就回来
I'll be right back.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好了
Here we go.
我给你拿过来吧
Oh, I'll -- I'll come around to you.
好  谢谢
Oh, good. Thanks.
好的
Okay.
日期没错
Yep. Dates match.
是个好的开始
That's a good start.
好了  会议室在表A1.1
all right, conference room is on sheet A1.1.
房间尺寸应该是
And room dimensions should be
15英尺6英寸乘12英尺6英寸
15'6" by 12'6"?
Uh, 15'6" by 12'6".
太好了
Great.
骨折还是扭伤
Break or sprain?
你的脚
‭Uh, your foot.
扭伤
a sprain.
几个月前我开始越野跑
I started trail running a couple months ago
上周去跑了一次  没留意
went for a run last week, wasn't paying attention
一只脚碰到树根了
and got my foot snagged in one of the roots
把脚踝扭伤了
just twisted my ankle.
会议室的墙壁是不是有2英尺10英寸的
Do you have a setback for that conference-room wall
收进尺度
at 2 feet, 10 inches?
对  收进2英尺10英寸
yes, the wall is set back 2 feet, 10 inches.
目前不错
So far, so good.
其实没那么糟的  只不过我还有个八个月的孩子
It hasn't been that bad except I have an 8-month-old, so...
恭喜你
Oh, congratulations.
谢谢
Thanks.
基本上所有事都得我自己来
Been, you know, ‭kind of doing it on my own.
我哥哥在帮忙  因为我时间有点紧
My brother's been helping since I'm a little limited these days
开车载我之类的
driving me around and whatnot.
有家人在身边总是好的
Well, it's nice to have family around.
是啊
Yeah.
大多数时候还行吧
For the most part.
他努力了
He tries.
这才是最重要的  不是吗
That's the important thing, right?
-对  -好了
- Yeah. ‭- Okay.
看来是相同的
I think these are the same.
我遗漏了什么吗
Am I missing anything?
看起来一模一样
They look the same to me.
太好了
Great.‭
-太好了  -不用重新提交了
- Yes! - ‭No re-filing.
谢谢你
Ahh. Thank you.
谢谢你  雪莉
Uh, thank you, Shirley. God.
不客气
You're welcome.
你救了我一命
You saved my life.
我告诉你
I am telling you
我的老板真会杀了我的
my bosses would have murdered me.
我理解
I understand.
整个组织都由你来负责
You know, you're the only person in charge of organization
突然出了什么事都是你的错
and suddenly ‭everything's your fault, right?
当然你会明白了
I assume you would know all about that.
嗨  莉齐
Yo, Lizzie.
比尔  艾丹呢
Bill. Where's Aidan?
女士你好
Hey, lady.
他没事  但他很饿
He's fine, but he's very hungry.
-比尔  比尔  -他根本吃得停不下来
- Bill. Bill -- - And he's like a little eating machine.
-比尔  -你能闻闻这个吗
- Bill -- - Could you sniff this for me?
比尔  艾丹在哪
Bill! Where is Aidan?
他没事  他在车里
He's fine. He's in the Wrangler.
-闻闻这个  -什么
- Just take a smell because... - ‭What?
-有点臭了  -你把我孩子留在你的车里
- ... it's a little funky. - You left my child in your Jeep?!
对  我窗户留了缝
Yeah. I cracked the window, just --
-比尔  -怎么了
- Bill -- - ‭What?
-你闻闻  -把钥匙给我
- Check this -- - Just give me the keys.
-我才不闻  -你要去哪
- I'm not gonna check it! - Where ya going?
去找艾丹  因为你不能把婴儿留在车里
To get Aidan because you can't leave a baby in a car.
你什么毛病
What the hell is wrong with you?!
天啊
Oh, man.
-去  快去  -什么
- Get -- Go get the -- - ‭What?
-去抱孩子  比尔  -我怎么了
- Go get the baby, Bill. - ‭What did I do?
-帮帮她  -才一分钟
- Help her! - ‭Well, ‭it's only been a minute.
我又不知道
I didn't know!
抱歉
Sorry.
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
你该怎么办
What are you supposed to do?
这五分钟  你该在车里看孩子
You're supposed to watch a baby for five minutes in a car.
那有多难
How hard is that?
慢点  我穿着人字拖呢
Slow down. I'm wearing flip-flops.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     克里斯   杏仁斯嘉丽   窝车
艾丹怎么样了
How's Aidan?
他没事
Oh, he's fine.
就一小会儿没人看管  谢天谢地
He was only alone for a minute, thank God.
等等  怎么了
Wait. What -- What happened?
翻译     吃冰棒   AE_CassA_Wei
-那袋奶  -什么
- Your milk -- ‭- What?
它流得到处都是
Well, it -- it just kind of went everywhere.
翻译     肉松   喵球球
-你在说什么  -我真抱歉
- What are you talking -- - I am so sorry.
什么  天啊
What -- Oh, my God.
校对     喃喃
天啊  天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-我...  -不不不
- I -- I -- ‭- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
-雪莉  不能这样  -冷静  冷静
- Shirley, I can't! Shirley, that's not -- - A-All right, all right.
时间轴     念念   大葱
天啊  公司都不知道我来德州了
Oh, my God, they don't even know I'm in Texas!
听我说  我们这么办
L-Listen, ‭this is what we're gonna do.
我们这么办
This is what we're gonna do.
后期     8T
你把你那份图纸给我
‭You're gonna give me your copy
我替换一下就行了
and I'll trade them out.
总监     喃喃
不会让你陷入麻烦吗
W-won't you get in trouble?
两份完全一样嘛
They're exactly the same.
没人会知道的
No one has to know.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
-去吧  拿出来  -好
- Go on, Gettem. - ‭Okay.
好  如果你确定的话
Okay. Okay, if you're sure.
好
Okay.
真是太感谢你了
Thank you so much.
雪莉
Shirley...
这真是雪中送炭啊
I can't tell you ‭how much this means to me.
真的  你救了我一命
Really, you're a life-saver.
我们得团结
We need to stick together.
当妈妈本来就够难了
Being a mom is hard enough.
好了
All right.
正式生效啦
Let's make this official.
绝命律师
第四季 第九集
精彩继续  欢迎回到《新婚生活》
We have returned. Welcome back to "The Newlywed Game."
先生们  我们已经在卡片上记下了你们的预测
Gentlemen, we've recorded your predictions on cards.
现在卡片平放在你们腿上
You now have them flat on your laps.
记住
Remember, each time
如果你的预测和你妻子的相同
that your prediction matches your wife's answer
你们就能得五分  到最后
you get 5 points, and the one couple
得分最高的一对夫妻
with the most points at the end of the show
将赢得第二次美妙的蜜月
wins a great second honeymoon.
女士们  你们回来了  真是太好了
So, ladies, we are so thrilled that you did come back
接下来是第一道五分题
and here's your first question for 5 points.
告诉我  女士们  如果你是一条船
Tell me, ladies, if you were a boat
你的丈夫会觉得
does your husband think
最近你哪里进水进得最多
you've been taking in the most water lately
船尾
on your stern...
左舷  右舷还是船头
on your port side, on your starboard side, or on your bow?
天啊
他说你的船头进水进得多
He said you've been taking a lot of water in on your bow.
船头
Bow?
上半身是船头
The top half's the bow.
对  但是  好吧
Yeah, but -- ‭Okay.
我有点...你是说我头重脚轻
I -- I'm a little -- Are you saying I'm top-heavy?
-最近  -最近  是啊  好吧
- Lately. - ‭Lately? I guess. Okay.
你这是在发牢骚
Are you complaining?
绝对没有
No, not at all.
-你不喜欢她的"船头"  -我喜欢
- You don't like her bow? - I love her bow.
赫克托叔叔
我是拉罗
你认识我  对不对
这是"是"吗
他没反应就是"不"
谁的勇气威震米却肯四方
没错
我知道你还能思考
赫克托叔叔
你知道我今天早上在想什么吗
燃烧皮革和马毛填料的气味
你还记得吗
郁金香旅馆
你对那个人那么客气
结果他还不理你
小题大做就为了证明自己不害怕
他开旅馆之前是教授  你记得吗
他总挂在嘴边  好一个大学教授
你跟他慢慢来
他妻子在旁边听
那个混蛋对自己优美的西语可骄傲了
对他的书  对他的古董
但等烧起来
都是一样难闻
我从来没告诉过你  但是...
我又回去了
走过火焰  浓烟
里面太烫了  连鞋的橡胶底都有点化了
我知道那么做很蠢  但是...
我很多愁善感
我想拿件东西当纪念品
这么多年  我都一直珍藏着
我带过来了
你想看看吗
唤起了很多回忆  是吧
你记得那个人使劲按铃  叫服务员吗
叮叮叮
"Ding! Ding! Ding!"
你呢  给了这教授教训
弄好了  叔叔
很好
现在试试
再来  叔叔
就是这样
再来
这才是塞拉曼加家的人
抱歉他有点问题
I'm sorry he has a problem.
劳拉
Laura?
一定要坚持到底
‭Definitely follow-through.
坚持到底  是的
Follow-through. ‭Yeah.
本来一切都很好
Everything else is doing good
但后来他说"接下来呢"
but afterwards, he's like, "Okay, what's next?
-"咱们继续"  -真的吗
- Let's get up and go." - Oh, really?
是啊
Yeah.
你去买点果冻吧
Hey, why don't you, um, go get some Jell-O?
叔叔  我们现在来谈谈那个智利人
赫克托还是老样子
Same old Hector.
就想把所有人都杀光
Just wants to kill everybody.
你知道的  最大的煎饼不一定是最好的
You know, the biggest pancake is not the best pancake
不然他们就会管它叫
or they would call it
"最好的煎饼  碰巧也是最大的"
"The best pancake ‭that happens to be the biggest."
续杯吗
‭Top off?
但才不是  谢谢
But, no, it's the -- Thank you.
你们还要点什么吗
Can I get y'all anything else?
-饱了  -不用了  多谢
- Stuffed. - Uh, we're good. Thanks.
你不想再来一个汉堡吗
No, you don't want a whole other burger?
不用急  请随意
Whenever you're ready. No rush.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
你最好少喝点咖啡
You better take it easy with that stuff.
我们至少还要再开一小时车
Oh, we've still got at least at hour on the road.
要保持清醒
Gotta stay awake.
但等我们到家了你也得睡得着啊
Yeah, but you got to be able to sleep when we get home, too.
-你的听证会是什么时候  -11点
- What time is your hearing? - ‭11:00.
在下周
This time next week
我就能再次成为詹姆斯·麦吉尔先生了
I will once again be James McGill, Esquire.
是啊
Yes.
我已经想好新的执业方向了
And I already got a jump on my new practice.
-是吗  -是的
- Oh, yeah? - ‭Yeah.
做手机生意时的意外之喜
Unexpected bonus ‭of the drop-phone business --
我发展了不少客户
it turns out it's great for client development.
是啊  确实如此
Y-Yes, I-I guess that's true.
迟早有一天
Sooner or later
那些傻瓜们会需要找律师的
every last one of those idiots is gonna need an attorney.
当然了  他们都以为我叫索尔·古德曼
Of course, they all know me as Saul Goodman.
小问题而已
That's just details. ‭
必须得说  有许多人
Got to say, a lot of people
会乞求获得休·巴布诺的同等待遇
are gonna be begging for the old Huell Babineaux treatment.
什么待遇呢
And what's that?
咱俩的力量
Our powers...
合二为一
combined.
人们会出高价
People would pay top dollar
求我们帮忙摆平一件要命的官司
for us to undo a potentially life-ruining sentence.
我们的力量应该只用来行善
I think we should only use our powers for good.
我们对善的定义又是什么
What are we considering good as of...
-从今晚六点起  -这样吧
- 6 PM tonight? - ‭You know what?
就像波特·斯图尔特说的那样
It's like Potter Stewart said.
波特·斯图尔特
曾任美国最高法院大法官
遇到自会明白
We'll know it when we see it.
我们开了四百多公里来得州卢伯克耍诡计
We just drove 300 miles to scam Lubbock, Texas
好让你的委托人能多13%的分行面积
so that your client can have a 13% bigger bank branch.
别误解我
Don't get me wrong.
我享受这过程的每分每秒
I loved every second of it.
但那怎么算是用我们的力量行善呢
But how is that using our powers for good?
好吧
Okay. Fine.
好吧  遇到自会知道
Yeah. We'll know it when we see it.
我喜欢
I-I like it.
这个计划我能接受
It's a plan I can get behind.
很好
Okay.
再见
我已就位
I'm in position.
我们快准备好了  继续待命
We're almost ready here. Stand by.
收到
Copy.
怎么了
What's up?
我很抱歉
My apologies.
我们出了点小问题
We have a small problem.
有多小
How small?
红灯亮了
The red light.
这表示  该怎么说呢
It means there's no, uh -- how do you say --
三个爆点有一个的电路没有形成回路
continuity on the circuit of one of the three charges.
橙色的那个
The orange one.
可能是有根线松动了或接错了
There may be a loose or faulty wire.
我会去检查一下
I'll go in and check.
我以为你才是爆破专家
I thought you were the demolition expert.
这是我的工作  麦克
It's my job, Michael.
待命
‭Stand by.
收到  待命中
Copy. Standing by.
振作点
振作点  你个傻瓜
现在试试
应该已经准备好了  麦克
I think we're ready here, Michael.
一切正常
All green.
我们这边就绪了
We're good here.
-准备好了  -是
- Ready? - ‭Go.
行动
Call it.
行动开始
On the go.
五
Five...
四
four...
三
three...
二
two...
一
one.
引爆
Now!
这就对了
等下
Oh, wait!
还少了个人
We're missing one!
少了个人
来喝一杯
Have a drink!
不了不了  我不喝  谢谢
No, no, no, no. I'm good. Thank you.
不行  这个我们不接受
No. We don't accept this.
你不可能永远在值勤  麦克
You can't be always on duty, Mike.
麦克  麦克  麦克
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
麦克  麦克  麦克...
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
干得漂亮
你在想什么
What's on your mind?
没什么  真的
Nothing, really.
很高兴爆破进展顺利
I'm pleased the blasting went well.
没有损伤墙体结构
No damage to the structure
没出什么意外事故
no unforeseen incidents.
你看起来并不高兴
You don't seem pleased.
我只是有点累了
I'm just tired.
我需要知道发生了什么事
I need to know what's going on.
没事
Nothing is going on.
这项工程花费的时间比我预计的要长
This work is taking longer than I estimated.
-确实  -我很感谢你的双R
- It is. - And I appreciate the R and R.
孩子们  他们玩得很开心
The boys -- ‭ they had fun.
但我...
But I'm...
麦克  你结婚了吗
Michael, you were married?
我结过婚
I was.
结了多久
How long?
二十二年
22 years.
或许你能理解
Perhaps you will understand.
-我四月就满二十六年了  -恭喜
- 26 in April. - ‭Congratulations.
我妻子
My wife.
我...
I'm...
离开了她  我...
I'm -- without her, I am adr--
漂浮在外
Adrift.
对  离开她漂浮在外
Yeah. Adrift without her.
你之前也离开过
You've been away before.
当然  但没像这样过
Yes, of course. Not like this.
我会做完手头上的工作
I'll finish what I've started
这个毫无疑问
no question of that.
但我还是忍不住去想
Still, ‭I can't help but wonder --
不  当然不会
No, of course not.
-什么  -不可能的
- What? - ‭It's impossible.
尽管
Although...
卡伊能在我回来之前监督工程
Kai could supervise the work until I get back.
我不想让你为难
I don't wish to cause you hardship
虽然我只想离开
even though I'd only be gone
一共大概四五天
for four days or five, maybe, total.
你是说请假飞回德国
You're talking about flying to Germany for a weekend?
很快就回
Just a quick trip.
我可以留下详细的指导
I could leave detailed instructions.
不会耽误进展
The work would not be interrupted.
你想见你老婆
You wanna see your wife?
比什么都想
More than anything.
那就赶快完工
Then finish the job.
维纳  你可以的
Werner, you can do this.
克服险阻  闯过难关
You put your head down, and you push your way through.
等大功告成
When it's done
你也挣得盆满钵满
from the money you've made here
就再也不用离开你的妻子了
you'll never be away from your wife again.
当然
Of course.
你说得很有道理
Of course you're right.
是我异想天开了
Flight of fancy.
这样吧
I-I tell you what.
多给你一次和她的通话机会
We'll get you on the phone with her for an extra call.
明天打吧
We'll do it tomorrow.
谢谢你  我的朋友
Thank you, my friend.
坚持住
You hang in there.
弗林先生
Mr. Fring?
什么事  莱尔
Ah, yes, Lyle?
有个人进来了
There's a, uh, man who just came in.
有一阵子了
And I know that it's been a while
但我觉得他好眼熟
but I was just like, "He is so familiar."
我觉得是那些人中的一个
I think it's one of the guys that, you know
就是去年来找麻烦的那群人
made all the trouble last year.
不是那个带头的
Not, uh, the -- the main guy
所以我也不是十分肯定
which is why I'm not totally sure.
知道了
I see.
不过他也没干什么
He's not doing anything, though.
他和另一个人点了点吃的
Uh, he and the other guy ordered some food
只是坐着
and they're just sitting
但我觉得应该跟你说一声
but I -- I thought that you'd want to know.
谢谢你  莱尔
Oh, thank you, Lyle.
我来处理
I'll take care of it.
一切都还满意吗
Is everything to your liking?
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
这是我吃过的最好吃的鸡肉了
This is the best chicken I have ever had.
很高兴你能这么说
Well, ‭I'm delighted to hear that.
不  真的  我说真的
No, really. I'm serious.
外表酥脆  但又不会太柴
I mean, it's crispy, but it's not dried out
调味料真是太...
and the seasoning -- it's so...
有味了
flavorful.
谢谢
‭Well, thank you.
还有什么需要帮助的吗
Is there anything else I can do for you?
有没有可能
Is there any chance --
我知道答案可能是不
and I know the answer is probably no
但我能否与老板见上一面呢
but is it possible for me to meet the owner?
我就是老板
I am the owner.
真的吗
Really?
我还真是走运
How lucky for me.
你对加盟感兴趣吗
Would you be interested in franchising?
因为我非常想投资
Because I would be eager to invest.
或许我们该去我办公室
Well, perhaps we should go to my office
作进一步的交谈
where we can discuss it further.
太好了
Excellent.
-别浪费美食  -这边请
- Don't waste that. ‭- This way.
我能为你做什么呢  先生...
Now, what may I do for you, Señor...
塞拉曼加
Salamanca.
爱德华多·塞拉曼加
Eduardo Salamanca.
你可以叫我"拉罗"
But you can call me "Lalo."
你是古斯塔沃·弗林
And you're Gustavo Fring.
我仰慕你好几年了
I have been an admirer of yours for many years.
你有多少家这样的餐厅
You have how many of these restaurants?
-七家  -七家
- Seven. - ‭Seven.
白手起家
And starting from nothing.
太了不起了
That's incredible.
有什么需要我帮忙的吗
What may I do for you?
我是代表整个家族来的
I come here ‭on behalf of my entire family
向你表达最诚挚的感谢
to give you our deepest thanks.
为什么感谢我
Well, for what?
为什么
For what?
因为你救了赫克托的命
For saving Don Hector's life.
我刚刚拜访过他
I just visited him.
看见那样的一个人
You know, seeing a man like that
不能说话  几乎不能动
can't speak, can barely move
我想哭
I wanted to weep.
但情况本来可能会更糟
But it could have been worse.
瓦尔加告诉我
Varga tells me
当其他人都在忙着自保
that while everybody else was picking their asses
你却冲向他  拍击他的胸部
you rushed to him, struck him on the chest
把他救了回来
and brought him back.
这就是本能
It was simple instinct.
但是介于你们之间的过去
But still, with all the history between you two
你这是表示了和平的意愿
what you did was a gesture of peace.
至少这是我们的看法
Or at least, that's how we see it.
我很高兴听到这个
I'm very pleased to hear that.
瞧瞧我们  相处融洽
And here we are, getting along.
你是否想过埃拉迪奥先生可能是个精明的混蛋
也许他希望我们结下仇恨
他坐在泳池旁晒太阳  发号施令
而你的卡车运着货物  塞拉曼加则维持秩序
我没觉得有什么仇恨啊
真的吗
Really?
不过如果我们相处过于融洽
Still, if we were to get along too well
埃拉迪奥肯定不会喜欢  对吗
I'm sure Eladio ‭wouldn't like that, would he?
我对于现在的安排很满意
I am satisfied ‭with the current arrangement.
我跟你扯淡呢
I'm just shitting you.
你要反抗埃拉迪奥就是疯了
You would be crazy to go up against Eladio.
听着  我会待一段时间
Look, I'm gonna be in town for a while
以后再聊
so, uh, you know, we'll talk some more.
我们欠你的
We owe you.
如果你需要帮忙  就来找我
If you need a favor, I'm your man.
我也一样
Same.
当然
Naturally.
我会再回来吃鸡的
Oh, and I'll be back for that chicken, eh?
实在美味至极
It's too tasty to stay away from.
你说你一周拿六块
You say you pick up six keys a week?
是的
Yeah.
哪里
Where?
他在城外有一个养鸡场
He's got a chicken farm way out of town.
带我去
Show me.
麦吉尔先生  可以见你了
Mr. McGill, ‭we're ready for you now.
太好了
‭Great.
看起来你已经完成了
And it looks like you've completed
诉前转移项目
the Pre-Prosecution Diversion Program?
没错  三周半之前
That's right, three and a half weeks ago.
事实上
Actually, I believe
如果你浏览补充材料
if you look at ‭the supplemental materials
会有一封我监督人布拉德·马卡姆的信
there's a letter from my supervisor, Brad Markham.
好的
Good.
他说他对你的付出印象深刻
He says he was impressed with your commitment.
去年大部分时间
And for most of last year
你受雇于CC通讯
you've been employed at CC Mobile?
是个手机店
It's a cellphone store.
而且  还有一封信
And, again, there's a letter
来自我的经理  罗伯特·芬恩先生
from my manager, Mr. Robert Finn.
也在补充材料里
Uh, it's also in ‭the supplemental materials.
信上说你连续三个月
Says here you were part of something
都获得白银圈奖
called the Silver Circle three months in a row?
这是一个销售奖
It's a sales award.
芬恩先生和CC通讯的人都特别的慷慨
Mr. Finn ‭and the people at CC Mobile have been very generous.
你不用卖很多手机
You don't have to sell many phones
就可以拿奖  相信我
to get in the Silver, believe me.
什么促使你选择了这个特定领域
What made you choose that particular field?
实话说  生活所迫
Honestly, just, uh, to put bread on the table.
但是它让我重新认识了客户关系
But I would say it's given me a new outlook on client relations.
我的意思是  在处理过手机合约之后
I mean, after dealing with cellphone contracts
向客户解释法规应该十分容易
explaining statutes to my clients should be a cakewalk.
俗话说
Well, as the saying goes
法律不断在变化
the law is constantly changing.
你是否一直在
Have you been keeping yourself, uh
了解法规最新动态
apprised of the latest developments?
我一直在读律师期刊
I've been reading the Bar Journal.
最近引起我注意的是克劳福德诉华盛顿州一案
You know, what caught my eye recently was Crawford v. Washington.
你们有人关注那个吗
Any of you follow that?
和单方面审查的可接受性有关
That has to do with the admissibility of ex parte examinations?
那是一个最高法院的案子  不是吗
That was a-a Supreme Court case, wasn't it?
没错  怎么说的来着
That's right. How did it go?
"唯一能够满足
"The only indicium of reliability
"宪法要求的可靠性标准
sufficient to satisfy constitutional demands
"就是宪法本身规定的
is the one the Constitution actually prescribes --
"对质条款"
confrontation."
经典的斯卡利亚式判决
It's classic Scalia.
我不禁想到受害者
I can't help but think about victims
被迫在公开法庭上和袭击者对质
forced to confront ‭their assailants in open court
但另一方面
but on the other hand
第六修正案相当有力
the Sixth Amendment is pretty controlling.
对不起
I'm sorry.
看我  都开始讨论宪法问题了
I just -- I get rolling on constitutional questions.
简而言之  我一直在尽我最大的努力
Short answer, ‭I've been doing my level best.
麦吉尔先生  关于你当初被停职的原因
Well, Mr. McGill, is there anything you'd like to tell us
你有什么想告诉我们的吗
about the reasons you were suspended in the first place?
过去的一年里
This past year
这是我心中唯一在意的事
that's pretty much been the only thing on my mind.
我为我完全愚蠢的行为感到羞耻
And I'm humbled by the sheer stupidity of my actions.
悔恨都不足以形容
Remorse doesn't begin to cover it.
我不会找借口
I'm not gonna make excuses
因为我所做的事没有任何借口
'cause there's no excuse for what I did.
但是当我坐在这里时
But as I sit here
我可以向你保证那样的事情以后再也不会发生
I can assure you nothing like that will ever happen again.
绝对不会
Never.
好的
Well, all right.
似乎很令人满意
That would seem to be satisfactory.
梅格  有什么想说的吗
Meg, you have something?
麦吉尔先生  法律对你来说意味着什么
Mr. McGill, ‭what does the law mean to you?
法律
The law?
行  好的
Uh, yeah. Okay.
从小到大
Listen, growing up
都没想过要成为律师
becoming a lawyer was, uh, the last thing on my mind.
即使我想  我也没有脑子或是
Even if I wanted to, I didn't have the smarts
本事或是毅力去做
or the skills or the "Stick-to-it"-ivness.
但我碰巧和一些律师一起工作
But I happened to get a job with some attorneys
我不禁思考  也许我可以做到
and I couldn't help but think, "Maybe I could do that?"
体内的一股能量让我跃跃欲试
Something inside me made me want to try.
我的文凭上写着
Now, listen, my diploma says
"美属萨摩亚大学法学院"
the "University of American Samoa Law School,"
正如它听上去的那样
and that's exactly what it sounds like.
是一所函授学校
That's a correspondence school.
我希望它是"乔治城大学"或者"西北大学"
I wish it said "Georgetown" or "Northwestern."
但美属萨摩亚大学是唯一一所肯录取我的学校
But UAS -- that's the only one that would take me.
我跟你们说  我并非天生干这行的
'Cause let me tell you, I wasn't a natural.
课程  学习
I mean, the classes, the studying
过司法考试让我使尽了浑身解数
trying to pass the bar practically killed me.
我有十几次都想放弃了
I must have quit 10 or 12 times.
但我坚持下来  我很开心我做到了
But I kept coming back to it, and I'm -- I'm really glad I did
因为当我能为真正的委托人工作时
because when I got to work with actual clients
那种感觉无与伦比
there was nothing else like it.
我国司法体系很复杂
Our legal system is complicated
而且时常变化
and sometimes it could feel capricious
但这是目前最公正的体系了
but it's the closest thing to real justice that we've got.
这个体系的运行
And for it to work
需要最有活力  最有干劲的律师
it needs vigorous, passionate advocates.
帮助我的委托人
And helping my clients, you know
为他们辩护
arguing on their behalf --
是我做的最棒的事
that's the best thing I've ever done.
过去这一年
And this past year...
我非常想念这份事业
I've missed the hell out of it.
说得真好
That was very eloquent.
你的看法受到什么特别影响吗
Was there any particular influence on your views?
奖罚分明
Credit where credit is due.
美属萨摩亚大学
The University of American Samoa.
加油  小地蟹
Go, Land Crabs!
还有吗
Anything else?
没了
No.
-谢谢  -没了  好的
- Thank you. - ‭No? Good.
没别的事了
I think we have everything we need.
几天后  你会收到们的决议信
You'll be getting a letter with our decision in the next few days.
行
All right.
谢谢抽空  谢谢你们
Thanks for your time, all of you.
我以为他就在那儿
I thought he was right up there, you know?
不  他是审核流程的一部分
Yeah, no, he was part of the review process.
你以前跟他同事过
And you've worked with him before.
-人靠谱吗  -人很靠谱
- Good guy? - ‭Yeah, real good guy.
-麦吉尔先生  -正是
- Mr. McGill. - Yes.
我知道他们说会寄信给我
I know they said I'd hear from them
但你悄悄告诉我
but, uh, just between you and me
他们做了什么决议
uh, what did they decide?
你逗我呢吧
You got to be kidding me.
不
No.
不  不  不
No. No, no, no, no, no!
不
Oh, no!
等等
Hey, wait a minute!
你要拒了我
You're denying me?!
-我做错了什么  -麦吉尔先生
- What did I do wrong? ‭- Mr. McGill?
-我做错了什么  我不能
- What did I do wrong?! ‭- I can't --
麦吉尔先生  这地方不合适
Mr. -- Mr. McGill, this is not the place.
我面面俱到  请告诉我
Okay. I did everything right. Please tell me.
我们做决议也很苦恼
Look, these decisions are never easy.
快  得给我个解释
Okay, come on. I deserve an answer.
-拜托  -麦吉尔先生  我不能
- Please! - ‭Mr. McGill, I-I can't --
我面面俱到
I did everything right.
问题在于真诚
It was a question of sincerity.
在于什么
A w-what?
委员会有人觉得你...
Some members of the committee found you somewhat...
不真诚
insincere.
你可以明年再申请
You're free to apply again next year.
麦克
Hey, Mike.
剩下几个小子怎么样了
Well, how goes it with the dirty half-dozen?
在打排球
Playing volleyball.
卡伊有小动作
That guy Kai cheats.
维纳还在打电话
Werner still talking?
他们道别大概二十分钟了
Oh, they've been saying goodbye for about 20 minutes now.
说了什么
Anything of note?
新养了条狗
Uh, they got a new puppy
乱撒尿
and it's peeing everywhere.
谈了狗  房子
The dog, the house.
她背不好了  他一回去
Her back's acting up, so they want
他们就准备去巴登巴登泡温泉
to go to the springs at Baden-Baden once he gets back.
-跟往常一样  -是啊
- Sound like the usual. - ‭Yep.
他们大概说了一个半小时
They've been at it ‭almost an hour and a half.
需要我提醒他还能打十分钟吗
You want me to, uh, give a 10-minute warning?
不用
No.
随他打多久吧
Let him go on as long as he wants.
等等  行了
Wait. Okay.
他们快打完了
They're wrapping up.
她要去书友会了
She's got to get to book club.
我去看看周围
I'm gonna check the perimeter.
世界上最棒的律师
再一次
那样说没有问题  而且还会再改
We have no problem with that language and will adjust.
十五页第四款第二条有问题
We do have a concern on page 15, clause 4b.
第三段写着
‭Third paragraph begins
"赔偿  偿付和偿还的权利"
"The right to indemnification, payment, reimbursement."
-懂了吗  -我知道了
- Everyone with me? - Yes. I see it.
这显然是条支持获赔的"沙袋条款"
This is clearly a pro-sandbagging clause.
特洛伊  这只是给了我们因违反代理协议
Troy, it simply gives us the right to indemnification
而获得赔偿的权利
for breaches of representation.
但其实没有违反
Of which there are none.
我觉得有必要
We feel it's necessary
考虑到目前谈判进展很迅速
given the fast pace of the negotiations thus far
我们又没有时间完成尽职调查
and the lack of time we've had to complete due diligence.
进展是由梅萨维德说了算
Mesa Verde set the pace here.
而且  这么做太过了
Further, you're overstepping
要求部分支付作为担保
by requiring parts of the target payment be put aside as collateral.
我是金·韦克斯勒  我提醒一下
Kim Wexler here. If I may respectfully remind you
梅萨维德允许你们保留一条
Mesa Verde is allowing you to keep a clause
违反担保必须是实质性的
that warranty breaches must be in a material respect.
这只是规范说法
It's standard language.
我们也很规范
Y-- As is ours.
各位  做些让步吧
Come on. ‭Guys, meet me halfway here.
行
Fine.
那我们来谈谈
Then we'd like to discuss
合同里怎么定义"知晓"
how we're defining ‭"Knowledge" within the contract.
请说
Be my guest.
我们认为现在的定义很合理
We feel ‭that what we've established is pretty reasonable.
-我们的客户提出  -喂
- Our clients would like to propose... - Hey there.
把"据卖方知晓"
...changing ‭"Within the seller's knowledge"
改为"据卖方最大程度知晓"
to "To the best of the seller's knowledge."
-慢点  -没事  但你得给我们机会
- Slow down. - That's fine, but you have to give us a chance to...
慢点
Slow down.
不真诚  不真诚
Insincere! Insincere?!
-吉米  怎么了  -再等一年
- Jimmy, what happened? ‭- A goddamn year?
我这一整年该干什么
What am I supposed to do for a whole year?!
-吉米  -我向你保证
- Jimmy -- ‭- I can guarantee you
我接下来一年绝对不他妈卖手机了
I'm not selling cellphones for a fuckin' year.
-绝对的  -他们到底说了什么
- I'll tell you that. - What did they say, exactly?
-怎么会  -被拒了
- How -- How did it -- - Hard pass!
-好吧  -别跟我说我可以上诉
- All right. - ‭And don't tell me I can appeal
因为上头一听到"不真诚"  我就完了
because once the board hears the word "Insincere," I'm screwed.
-吉米  吉米  -"不真诚"要怎么洗白呢
- Jimmy -- Jimmy -- ‭- How do you ‭disprove "Insincere"?!
吉米  你缓缓
Please, Jimmy, just take a breath
拜托你从头开始讲
and start ‭from the beginning, please.
我表现很好  金
I was good, Kim.
我没有自大  我很了解该说什么
I mean, I-I wasn't stuck up, but I knew my shit, right?
他们问"你停职期间都在做什么"
"What have you been doing during your suspension?"
还问"你有一直跟进法律领域的动态吗"
and, uh, "Have you been keeping up with the law?"
我都回答的很好
Yadda yadda. All fine.
然后他们其中一个  莫名其妙地
And then one of them, out of nowhere
问了一个很怪的问题
comes up with ‭this weird-ass question --
"法律对你来说意味着什么"
"What does the law mean to you?"
这可是个大问题
That's a big one.
巨大的问题  但我回答的很好
Huge! And I nailed it!
我讲了法律的意义
I talked about the meaning of the law
我踏实而谦虚
and I was down-to-earth and I was humble
而且我还很真诚  他们很喜欢
and I was sincere and they loved it.
-结果  -结果他们拒绝了我
- So... - So they turned me down.
肯定还有什么别的吧
Well, there has to be more to it than that.
没别的了
There's not.
我不
I don't --
你说到查克的时候怎么说的
What did they say ‭when you talked about Chuck?
关查克什么事
What does Chuck have to do with this?
什么
What?
所以你根本就没
Well, so, you didn't even...
我为什么要提
Why would I?
好吧  那好
Okay. O-- Um...
这样  我们来想办法
Okay, listen, we will figure this out.
你要上诉  我们上诉给
And, yes, you will appeal. We'll appeal this to the --
-他们会直接定论的  -那我们就不让他们定
- They're just gonna rubber-stamp. - Well, we won't let them.
他们不论如何都会的
They're gonna ‭rubber-stamp whatever
我们想办法让你看上去真诚
And we'll find a way to make you look sincere.
-金  我很真诚了  -我知道
- Kim, I was sincere! ‭- I know that.
我是说我们来想办法
I meant ‭we will fix it.
我可能说的有点俗  但我都是认真的
I might have been a little corny, but I meant every word.
我知道
I know that.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
-我当然相信了  -天啊
- Of course I do. ‭- Jesus.
我看你表情就知道了
It's right there on your face.
在你眼里我就像下作的混蛋
You think I'm some kind of lowlife, some kind of asshole...
-什么  -就像是坏人才会请的律师吧
- What? - The kind of lawyer guilty people hire, right?
没有  吉米  不是
No. Jimmy, that's not --
你眼里的我就是"风流吉米"
Yeah, you look at me, and you see Slippin' Jimmy.
我从没这样说过
I never said that.
但你就是这样想的
Yeah, but you thought it!
你想知道为什么委员会说你不真诚吗
You want to know why the committee called you insincere?
因为你没有提到查克
Because you didn't mention Chuck.
为什么一定要提
What does that have to even --
他们看了资料
They read the transcripts.
他们知道发生了什么  吉米
They know what happened, Jimmy.
他们等着你说查克的事情
They were waiting for you to say something about him.
所以我应该长篇大论地
So I'm supposed to make a big hairy deal
在我的复职听证上说我死去的哥哥吗
about my dead brother at my re-instatement hearing?
这怎么就真诚了
How is that sincere?
我从来不想查克的事  好吗
Ya, I don't ‭think about Chuck, okay?
我不想念查克
I don't miss Chuck.
查克以前在世  现在不在了  就这么回事
Chuck was alive and now he's dead and that's that.
事情结束  生活继续  怪我咯
Finito. Life goes on. So sue me.
你又是这幅表情
There it is again.
-这就是为什么我们没有办公室  -什么  不是
- That's why ‭we don't have an office. - What? No!
拜托你  不要扯到办公室上
Just, you know, ‭do not start in on that office.
我不想再听到你说
I don't want to hear another word
那个愚蠢的办公室了
about that stupid office.
愚蠢的办公室  好  你接着说  你接着说
Stupid office? Okay. Here we go. Here we go.
吉米  从一开始我就一直站在你这边
Jimmy, I have been on your side since the day we met!
是谁因为你一个电话赶来
Who comes running when you call?
谁给你收拾残局
Who cleans up your messes?
我也是有工作的
I have a job
但我每次为了你  什么都放下了
but I drop everything for you every single time.
你在磁带里坦白了重罪
You confess to a felony on tape
我帮了
I'm there.
你受审讯  我做你的律师
You have a bar hearing, I represent you.
一次又一次  你需要我  我就帮忙
Over and over again, if you need me, I'm there.
但你脑海里衡量我对你的感情
But somehow in your mind the only measure
就靠一个什么办公室
of my feelings for you is -- is some office?!
我能跟你同居  跟你睡觉
I'm good enough to live with, to sleep with
但你就是不能跟我共事
but God forbid you should have an office with me.
什么  我刚跟你说过
What are you t-- I just told you
你对自己的生活感到有点无聊了
‭You get ‭a little bored with your life
-你就委身趟趟浑水  -那
- so you come down ‭and roll around in the dirt... - That's...
-跟"风流吉米"玩玩  -有那么好玩吗
- have some fun with Slippin' Jimmy... - Oh, is it fun?
-然后你就回去了  -向助理地检撒谎
- ...and then it's ‭back up. - Fun like lying to the ADA
捞你的朋友出来好玩吗
to get your friend out of the shitter?
还是说我一脸职业假笑听你
Or fun like standing there with a smile plastered on my face
跟我的律师同事玩幼稚的脑筋急转弯
while you play infantile mind games on my law partner?
带我到你高高在上的办公室真是个大错误
Oh, what a mistake it was to take me up ‭to your office in the sky!
-下次请别再带我去了  -也许我不会了
- You'll never do that again! - ‭Yeah, maybe I won't.
可能下次你打电话  我也不来了
And maybe next time you call, I won't come.
你又来了  落井下石
There you go. ‭Kick a man when he's down.
吉米  你从来就在井里
Jimmy, you are always down.
我全搞砸了
I messed it all up.
你还想做律师吗
You still want to be a lawyer?
想啊
Yeah.
那我们可以从这点做起
Well, we can start with that.
嗨  麦克
Hey, Mike.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你  先生
Oh, thank you, sir.
情况如何
So, what do we got?
挺安静的
It's pretty quiet.
卡伊又起迟了
Kai was up late again.
他下去一个小时以后
About an hour after he went down
维纳出来了几分钟
Werner came out for a couple minutes.
然后大约两点半的时候  卡斯珀起来了
Then Casper was up around 2:30
看了会电视又进去了
watched some TV, headed back in.
六号这怎么回事
What's going on with 6?
这里  这是什么
There -- what is that?
哦这个  有几个像素挂了
Oh, yeah. Dead pixels.
昨天还没有的
Wasn't there yesterday.
之前忽然有一次电压突增
Had a voltage spike earlier.
忽然雪花了大概二十秒
Camera flared for about 20 seconds
但是立即又好了
but it came right back.
电压突增
A voltage spike?
其他的摄像头有过吗
Any of the other cameras do that?
有过  10号
Yeah. 10.
让我看看外面的摄像头
Show me the outside cameras.
你跟我走
You -- let's go.
开灯
Get the lights!
上面  你去查查
Up there. You check that out.
怎么回事
‭‭What's going on?
麦克
Mike?